{
    "subject": "resource/Inception",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2010s_science_fiction_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Inception is Category:2010s science fiction films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9545478820800781,
            "question": "What makes Inception a notable film within the 2010s science fiction genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7171748876571655,
            "question": "In what years were films typically released in the category of 2010s science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7124962210655212,
            "question": "What impact did Inception have on subsequent science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6792057752609253,
            "question": "How does Inception compare to other popular science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565091013908386,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in 2010s science fiction films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6396585702896118,
            "question": "What genre is the film Inception?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6364555358886719,
            "question": "Did Inception receive critical acclaim for its science fiction elements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6355312466621399,
            "question": "What technological advancements were depicted in Inception that reflected trends in the 2010s?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6272229552268982,
            "question": "What decade is the film Inception categorized under?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.59349125623703,
            "question": "Are there any other examples of science fiction films from the 2010s?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Inception is Category:2010s science fiction films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5789_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade is the film Inception categorized under?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5789_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What technological advancements were depicted in Inception that reflected trends in the 2010s?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5789_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Inception receive critical acclaim for its science fiction elements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5789_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5789_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n**Triple:** Inception is a film that stars Leonardo DiCaprio and Christopher Nolan.\n\nGiven the context information, here are the supporting documents:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5789/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt\n* The film stars Leonardo DiCaprio as a thief who steals secrets from people\u2019s subconscious.\n* Directed by Christopher Nolan, it made ~US$828 million and debuted number one in the box office on its opening weekend.\n\n**Evaluation:**\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. Both documents mention Leonardo DiCaprio as the star of the film and Christopher Nolan as the director.\n\n**Response:** \n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided clearly mention that \"Inception\" is a representative text of the 2010s decade and falls within the category of a science fiction film, supporting the query statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}